{
    "id": "e9e2139e4ac04a878da8cbbe6befdf7b",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. we visit Ajanta and Ellora? (Making a suggestion)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you come with us? (Asking a question)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he play for our team? (Asking a question about future possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. they advertise the post? (Asking a question about future possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. I get a prize if I stand first in the examination?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The Captain said, ‘Players ………………… assemble at the College at 4 P.M.’ (obligation)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He said, ‘The scoundrel ……………….. thrashed.’ (necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be",
                "shall be",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. not be unfair to him. (duty)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………. all work for the common good. (duty or necessity",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………. tell the truth. (obligation)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}